[
        {
            
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Where was Beyoncé born?",
            "correct_answer": "Dallas, Texas",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Houston, Texas",
                "Paris, France",
                "Baltimore, Maryland"
            ]
        },
        {
            
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What Group is Beyonce Associated with?",
            "correct_answer": "Destiny's Child",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "TLC",
                "Run DMC",
                "ACDC"
            ]
        },
        {

            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "What is Beyonce's Middle Name?",
            "correct_answer": "Giselle",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Amanda",
                "Cathy",
                "Riri"
            ]
        },
        {
           
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Who runs the world?",
            "correct_answer": "Girls, girls",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Boys, boys",
                "Birds, birds",
                "Cats, cats"
            ]
        },
        {
        
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Beyoncé made her big screen debut in what movie?",
            "correct_answer": "Austin Powers",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Dream Girls",
                "The pink Panther",
                "The social network"
            ]
        },
        {
   
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "What is the name of Beyoncé's all-female tour band?",
            "correct_answer": "Suga Mama",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Jenga",
                "Beyonders",
                "Parliment Funkadelic"
            ]
        },
        {
            
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "What does Beyoncé call her alter ego?",
            "correct_answer": "Sasha",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mia",
                "Singing Fish",
                "Sardeen"
            ]
        },
        {
            
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "What brand carries Beyonce's perfume line?",
            "correct_answer": "Tommy Hilfiger",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Machiavelli",
                "Jordache",
                "Rami Levi"
            ]
        },
        {
            
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "How are the Beyoncé fans called",
            "correct_answer": "Bey Hive",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Bey Hey",
                "Bee wow",
                "Bey Baby"
            ]
        },
        {
            
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In which animated film of 2013 Beyoncé lent her voice to Queen Tara?",
            "correct_answer": "Epic",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Frozen",
                "Plans",
                "Ice Age"
            ]
        }
    
]